pakmcqs.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy - PakMcqs

**PRIVACY POLICY**

The Personal information, email that submitted while registering to the site, will NOT be distributed, shared with any other third-parties. We only use this data for our information, for research, to improve our services and for contacting you purposes. PakMcqs.com is an Open Database Site, so Registering into site is NOT mandatory and also we won’t verify your email address. Registration into the site is purely of user’s interest. PakMcqs.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Any significant changes will be notified to you by sending an email to your email address that you provided while registering with us or by placing a notice on our site.

 **ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS**

PakMcqs.com provides its services to you with Terms listed. These policies are not final and may be updated by us from time to time without notice of you. So visit this page for latest updated policies.

 **USAGE OF THIS SITE**

PakMcqs.com is an Open Database and operates with a motto of collecting and sharing multiple choice questions and answers that were asked in various interviews or in admission tests in various institutes and universities of Pakistan. This data of multiple choice questions is collected and submitted by various users/visitors around the world. PakMcqs.com does not guarantee the re-occurrences or repetition of questions in same interviews/tests or any other interviews / tests. The purpose of this site is to provide information to the public specially to students and job seekers. Even though every care has been taken in compiling the information forwarded by certain enthusiastic users, PakMcqs.com doesn’t guarantee the accuracy of the content or information that provided in this site and won’t take responsiblity for any INCORRECT questions, answers, content and any form of errors. if you think any Answer of the Multiple choice question is wrong then user/visitor of the site can submit their comment on each mcqs. or simple contact us. PakMcqs.com will not be responsible in anyway for any damages/consequences that might occur due to inclusion of some incorrect content or information in this site. You can use this information solely at your own risk. Users submitting questions or answers or code to this site, asserts that he or she owns that data or otherwise has the right to redistribute it freely. PakMcqs.com assumes no liability for disputes regarding ownership, copyright, or trademarks of the data submitted to this site. PakMcqs.com reserves the right to refuse to post any submission, to alter submissions, and to remove a submission from the site. PakMcqs.com may exercise this right without any advance notice to the individual submitting the code or content. All trademarks and company names published in this site are subjected to their respected owners and companies.

 **REGISTRATION INTO SITE**

This is an OPTIONAL service provided by www.PakMcqs.com. so Visitors can register into the site on their own interest, it is not mandatory. This registration into the site permits the user to maintain and modify of the data submitted to the site. The personal information that collected during this registration process will NOT, be distributed and shared with any other third-parties. While submitting registration form, you also agreed to provide and maintain true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted by the Service’s registration form. PakMcqs.com NEVER verifies the accuracy of Personal Information that is submitted to the site, it is solely responsibility of the user. PakMcqs.com reserves the right to suspend or permanently delete any user, If the data or information provided by the user is inaccurate, not related or incomplete or if the user violated our terms and conditions in any manner.

 **ANTI-SPAM POLICY**

PakMcqs.com is against in sending spam, unsolicited emails. You should not use our service and you are not authorized to use our referral or email services, for your personal or commercial purposes. By usage of this service you agreed that to our policies. Violating these policies in any manner subject to violation of respected laws and necessary action will be initiated against the defaulters.

 **COPYRIGHT POLICY**

PakMcqs.com holds the property of all the pages, data and graphics presented on the website.

All the pages mcqs data of PakMcqs.com may not be reproduced or redistributed in any shape or form without written permission of PakMcqs.com and we allow our users/visitors of site to share our mcqs data on all social networking site with link to PakMcqs.com

PakMcqs.com respects the copyrights, trademarks and intellectual property of others and also expect the same from other users. On PakMcqs if anyone found any data or information that is owned by him or any content that violates someone’s intellectual property rights, please contact to us with all necessary documents/information that authenticate his authority on property.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

Where necessary, this site uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

 **Controlling Your Privacy**

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

 **About Google Advertising**

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google’s cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

About Google advertising: What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher’s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. (Hyperlink this to: http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/

 **If you’re using this site then you must agree with Privacy Policy provided above.**
